showtime.com 2003-12-02

# Showtime.com StubHub Shania Twain tickets, Neil Young

| | 

Privacy Policy  [](https://www.truste.org/validate/14023 "TRUSTe: Click to Verify")

**Overview** StubHub is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to enable individuals and organizations to establish trusting relationships based on respect for personal identity and information by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the site stubhub.com. Because StubHub wants to demonstrate its commitment to our users' privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

Users with questions or concerns regarding their privacy or this statement should contact StubHub Customer Service at:

LiquidSeats   
3435 Cesar Chavez  
Suite 206  
San Francisco, CA 94110  
email: [custserv@stubhub.com](mailto:custserv@stubhub.com)  
Telephone: 1-866-STUBHUB (1-866-788-2482)

If they do not receive acknowledgment of their inquiry or their inquiry is not satisfactorily addressed, they should then contact TRUSTe through the [TRUSTe Watchdog Dispute Resolution Process (http://www.truste.org/watchdog.html)](http://www.truste.org/watchdog.html). TRUSTe will serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve users concerns. 

**Information Collection** _What We Collect_  
When you **browse** through our site we collect: 
      * basic information about your computer, browser and connection to make sure that we can give you proper information and customer service and for security purposes;
      * aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit to improve our site.  
If you choose to **register** so you can buy or sell tickets we will ask you for more information including:
      * your name and address so that we can have your tickets picked up or delivered to you;
      * your email address and telephone number so we can contact you;
      * your date of birth so we can ensure all of our users are adults and for general demographic information;
      * a login and password to use to update your information at any time in the future;
      * Also on this page we will give you the option to choose if you would like to receive email or written service from StubHub. If you would like to receive these solicitations simply check the appropriate box. You can choose to stop participating at any time simply by changing your preferences on the website, replying to an email's Unsubscribe, or contacting our Customer Service.
  
_CoBrand Partners_  
As indicated herein your information on co-branded pages hosted by Stubhub is collected by co-branded partners. On co-branded sites (e.g. sites that appear labeled with another company's logos) contact information and transaction data (not including credit card numbers) for customers who registered or transacted through the partner's co-branded 'StubHub' are essentially shared with the owner of that co-branded website (typically co-owned). Your choices about being contacted are included with that information so that partner may respect your preferences. However, please understand Stubhub/LiquidSeats does not control information actually owned by co-branded partners. Please refer to their respective privacy policies for information on how they will handle your information. 

If you choose to **buy or sell** tickets we will ask you for: 

      * credit card information to complete your transaction (for buyers) or to verify your identity (for sellers). You may choose whether to store your credit card info for future use.
      * Shipping address so tickets can be shipped to the location of your choice
  
_Changing and Updating personal information_   
Consumers can change all of their personal account information by going to the My Info section of My Account on StubHub at https://www.stubhub.com/my.cfm. You can change your address, telephone number, email address, password, credit card info, as well as your privacy settings. _Supplementation of Information_   
In order for this Web site to properly fulfill its obligation to protect all of its users, it is necessary for us to verify your credit card information with Verisign, a 3rd party. This is done for verification purposes only; we store no additional data with your profile.    
**Profile** We store information that we collect through cookies and log files to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. _Cookies_   
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user.s computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. 

By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still browse our site, however they will not be able to buy or sell tickets. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

_Log Files_   
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring pages, platform type, date/time stamp. IP addresses, etc. are linked to personally identifiable information. We use Log Files for error diagnostics, session management and to determine our advertising efficacy.    
**Communications from the Site** _Special Offers and Updates_   
Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections. _Transactions_   
Members who buy or sell tickets will receive a number of emails throughout the transaction process and they may sometimes receive phone calls from our Customer Service department to ensure smooth transactions. _Newsletter_   
If a user wishes to subscribe to HubBub, our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections. _Service Announcements_ < br> On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. _Customer Service_   
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.    
**Sharing** At StubHub, we care about your privacy. We will never share your credit card number or any other financial information with any third party. We may share your personal information with third parties in the following instances: _Legal Disclaimer_   
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. _Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)_   
We share some aggregated demographic information (age, zip codes) with some of our partners. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. _CoBrand Partners_   
Contact information and transaction data (not including credit card numbers) for customers who registered or transacted through a partner's cobranded StubHub are essentially shared with the owner of that cobranded website. Your choices about being contacted are included with that information so that partner can respect your preferences. Refer to that website.s privacy policy for information on how they will handle your information. _Third Party Intermediaries_   
We use FedEx and some couriers to ship tickets, Verisign to process credit card transactions, and PayPal to disburse payments to sellers. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. _Business Transitions_   
In the event StubHub goes through a business transition, such as a merger, an acquisition by another company, or a sale of a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days after a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the users' personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section.    
**Security** This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just 'surfing'. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users' information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, behind a locked cage at a professional hosting company. 

_Changes to this Statement_   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Material changes to this policy will be posted on this website 30 days prior to execution. 

Effective 07/08/2002 

|
